結束バンド
４人そろっての初ライブは
Kessoku Band managed to succeed
in its first full four-member concert.
なんとか成功を収めて
こうして私たちの夏は 終わ…
And so, our summer came to...
August
らなかった
a middle.
That's right. We do have
some break left, don't we?
考えてみれば
休みは まだ残ってるもんね
Until my summer break comes to an end...
夏休み 最後まで
What lovely weather!
今日も いい天気ね
一日 一日を…
I'm going to spend every single day
enjoying it to its fullest.
大切に楽しんで
お手！
Shake!
フウ～
Another fulfilling day...
今日も充実した一日…
Not!
じゃない！
It's summer break, but I'm not
doing a single thing differently!
August
夏休みなのに
やってることが いつもと一緒！
I mean, playing guitar is fun and all, but...
いや ギター弾くのは楽しいけど
結束バンドのみんなと
遊ぼうと思って
I was thinking Kessoku Band
might hang out together,
so I've cleared my schedule
of everything but work, but...
バイト以外
ずっと予定 空けてるけど
Of course, it's usually
clear regardless, but...
いや ふだんから
予定は空いてるけど
B-But keeping it clear
has a totally different feel, right?
で… でも
空いてるのと 空けてるのは
気持ちが全然違うわけで
Still, even at work, nobody
so much as suggests hanging out...
バイトで会っても みんな
全く遊びの話をしてこないし
Bocchi-chan! See you at work again tomorrow!
ぼっちちゃん
明日のバイトも よろしくね
The members of a band usually
hang out, don't they?
バンド仲間だし
みんなで遊ぶとかじゃないのかな？
But I guess when we're all
available, we should be practicing...
４人で集まれる日があるなら
練習したほうがいいもんね
S-Still, just for once, I'd like to...
で… でも
一度くらいは みんなで…
うん そうだよ
受け身でいたらダメだ！
Yeah, that's right!
Kessoku Band
Can anyone take my shift
tomorrow? I've got stuff to do ^^;
I can take it!
GRATITUDE
I can't always be passive!
B-But if I bring it up,
で… でも 私が誘ったら
I'm the one who'll have to pick
the place and time...
私が場所とか時間
決めないといけないだろうし
あああ～！
I can't think of a plan
that'll satisfy everyone!
みんなを満足させられるような
プランが思いつかない
Nijika
But I just have to work up the courage!
いや でも やっぱり
ここは思い切って
I'll start with Nijika-chan!
まずは 虹夏ちゃんに…
Nijika
Message                                Mobile                             Video
うっ うぐぐぐ…
まっ まあ 今日は もう遅いから
Well... It's a bit late to call now.
ひとりちゃ～ん ご飯よ～
Hitori-chan! Time to eat!
A-Anyway, there's a lot of summer break left!
まっ まあ まだ夏休みはあるんだし
I'm sure one of them will make
the offer sooner or later.
きっと そのうち
誰かが誘ってくれるよね
Yay!
イエ～イ！
What is the general theory of relativity?
The general theory of relativity
一般相対性理論は
states that the passage of time slows
in the presence of a powerful gravity well.
Time slows due to curvature of spacetime caused by a powerful gravity well
強い重力が働くと
時間が遅れる
とされています
Artist's impression of a black hole drawing in matter
The black holes theorized
to exist throughout space
宇宙空間に
存在するといわれる
ブラックホールは
are believed to be the end state
of the life cycle of massive stars.
質量がとても大きな星の
最期の姿と考えられ
Their extreme density and
high gravitational potential
極めて高密度で強い重力のため
mean that not only matter, but even light,
becomes trapped forever in their pull.
物質だけでなく 光さえも
脱出することができない天体です
ひとりちゃ～ん 入るわよ～
The gravitational field causes time to slow
so much that it nearly stops...
Hitori-chan! I'm coming in!
いい天気だから
お布団 干そうと思って
I thought I'd air out the futons
while the weather's nice.
Don't lie around all day, all right?
いつまでも
ダラダラしてちゃダメよ
You'll be back at school soon.
そろそろ新学期でしょ？
But I'm in a black hole.
ここはブラックホールだから…
August 30th
Sis
another day
nowhere
lying around
really
funny
It's done!
出来た！
I liked dark, cramped spaces,
so I'd bury my face deep in my hood
My eyes resented the heartless world,
but yearned for love
I liked being soaked by the rain,
because my face looked better clouded over
I pretended to be afraid of the storm
while waiting for the sky to burst
Strum through the light's distortion
I want to make thunder roar
Drum beyond the pain
What can I do? This fierce
pounding is out of control
Strum in a harmonizing quartet
I want to cause a revolution
Drum in a lamenting forte
What can I do? My savage
nature is beyond wild
BOCCHI THE ROCK!
#09 Enoshima Escar
ぼっちちゃんの様子が変？
Bocchi-chan? Acting strange?
Yeah.
そうなんです
ここ数日 目は うつろで
会話も ままならなくて
She's been staring out into space,
and she's barely talked in days.
それ いつもどおりのぼっち
Sounds like typical Bocchi.
C'mon, you can't possibly...
いや そんなことは…
Astaxanthin. Canthaxanthin.
アスタキサンチン
カンタキサンチン…
...be exaggerating.
あるか
ないです！
I'm not!
She seemed on the verge
of tears for a minute,
だって
泣き始めたかと思えば
but then she spontaneously
started dancing the samba!
急に陽気になって
サンバを
踊り始めるんですよ
Tortilla!
トルティーヤ！
That's not good!
それはヤバいわ
Typical Bocchi.
いつもどおりのぼっち
違います！
It is not!
Hey.
お～い
ん？
ちょっと ぼっちちゃんに
あれ やめさせてくんない？
Could you get Bocchi-chan to knock it off?
Eh?
“あれ”？
朝から あの調子で
ライブハウス前に
She's been making cicada graves
in front of the club all day.
セミのお墓 作り続けてんだよね
That's way too out there!
限界すぎる！
なんで変になってんの？
What's got her freaking out like that?
I wonder if it's because today's
the last day of summer break.
夏休みが
今日で終わるからでしょうか？
Farewell. Farewell.
I don't wanna go back to school either.
新学期は私も嫌
Say, guys.
っていうかさ
お前ら この夏 どこか
遊び 誘ってやったの？
Have you actually taken her out
anywhere this summer?
えっ？
なんか この前バイトんとき
休み何してるかって話になって
One time, while you were working, I asked
what she was doing with her time off...
Bocchi-chan. What are you doing with
your break when you're not working?
ぼっちちゃん 夏休み
バイトない日 何してんの？
Um, I... My little sister asked me
to teach her guitar, so I did.
あっ えっと い… 妹に
ギター教えてって言われて
教えたりしました
Hey, that's nice.
へえ～ いいじゃん
で… でも
B-But...
Today I asked my sister
to teach me to play guitar!
“今日はお姉ちゃんに
ギターを教えてもらいました”
I thought it was awesome how my sister
stayed inside practicing, day after day!
“お姉ちゃんは いつでも家にいて
ギターを練習して”
“すごいなと思いました”
“ふたりは夏休み
やること いっぱいだし”
I have too many things to do and too many
friends to play with over summer break,
“友達とも遊ばなきゃだから”
so I can't stay home practicing
every day like her!
“お姉ちゃんみたいに
毎日 練習できないので”
That's why I think it's awesome!
“すごいなと思いました”
H-Her words sent me into a spiral, and
I ended up not getting out of bed for days.
い… 妹の言葉について
考え込んでしまって
数日 寝込みました
I see.
そう…
I cleared my schedule!
予定は空けてます！
えっ？
N-Not because I have nothing to do!
I cleared it on purpose!
あ… 空いてるんじゃなくて
空けてるんです
おっ おう…
R-Right.
とか言ってたぞ
She said all that.
それ もっと早く教えてよ
Why didn't you tell us earlier?
I wanted to invite her, but...
誘おうとはしてたんですけど
My schedule's packed every day I'm not here,
ここに来る日以外は
全部 予定埋まってて
and I thought she'd be uncomfortable
around people she doesn't know, so...
知らない子いたら
後藤さん委縮しちゃうかなって
What about you, Ijichi-senpai?
伊地知先輩は？
あたしは…
W-Well, when we're not practicing, I'm
cleaning up at home or working here, so...
練習の日以外 家 片づけたり
ここでバイトしてたから
R-Ryo-senpai?
リ… リョウ先輩は？
I figured you two had invited her already.
２人が誘ってると思ってた
えっ じゃあ つまり…
Y-You're telling me...
誰も ぼっちちゃんと遊んでない
Nobody invited Bocchi-chan out?
お前ら もうバンド名 変えろよ
You guys need to change your band name.
G-Gotoh-san! You want to hang out?
ごっ ごごご… 後藤さん
遊び行かない？
ドコサヘキサエン酸
エイコサペンタ…
Docosahexaenoic acid. Eicosapentaenoic acid.
Come back to us!
戻ってきて！
I know! Let's all go to the
beach together, right now!
そうだ！　みんなで今から
一緒に海に行きましょうよ
We could hit up Enoshima!
江の島とか
Great idea! It's a straight shot
from Shimo-Kita.
いいね！
下北からなら１本で行けるし
B-But...
デ… デモ 今日ノ練習ハ
ドウスルンデスカ
What-about-our-practice-then?
Why's she talking like a robot?
なぜ 片言？
We can practice any time!
別に練習は いつでもできるし
まだ 次のライブも
決まってないしさ
It's not like we have our next
concert scheduled, anyway.
Let's use our last day of summer break
to make memories together!
みんなで 夏休み最後の
思い出作りをしましょう
思い出…
Memories...
Isn't that a great idea?
ね？　いいでしょ？
みんなで海 行こう！
Let's go to the beach together!
But it might be too late to swim.
でも 時期的に もう泳げなそう
Y-Yeah... no point in going to
the beach if you can't swim.
うう… 泳げないのに
海行く意味ないですよね
B-But there's still the beach shacks!
で… でも
海の家は まだあるはずよ！
Let's eat shirasu-don!
シラス丼 食べよ！
それで砂浜で海見たり
And we can gaze at the ocean from the sand...
Ocean... Sand...
海… 砂浜…
ね？
想像するだけで楽しいでしょ？
See? Doesn't that sound fun?
アハハハ！　待てって
Wait for me!
ん？
ウフフフ 待たな～い
You catch up!
きゃあ！
わっ
アハッ
ウフッ
The end of summer, huh?
夏も終わるね
Let's come again next year.
来年も一緒に来ようね
Tropical love forever!
トロピカルラブ フォーエバー
あうっ
えっ？
Tropical love...
トロピカルラブ…
後藤さん！
Gotoh-san!
Forever...
フォーエバ…
なんで そうなる？
Why is this happening?
I think I made it worse somehow.
なんか 追い打ち
かけちゃいましたけど
ん～
Okay! Let's take her out while she's docile!
よし！　また暴走する前に急ごう
ラジャ！
Roger!
喜多ちゃん！
ぼっちちゃんのこと よろしくね
Kita-chan, you carry Bocchi-chan!
What?!
えっ？
Okay! Let's get going to Enoshima!
よ～し
じゃあ 江の島へ レッツゴー！
ゴー
Yeah!
Gotoh-san! We'll be making
those summer memories soon!
後藤さん あと少しで
夏の思い出 できるからね！
Just hang in there a little longer!
もう少しの辛抱だから！
Scary... Tropical...
怖い… ト… トロピカル～
I'm in a black hole... at the
far reaches of the galaxy...
ここはブラックホール…
She must really hate school
to be acting this way.
こんなになるって
よっぽど学校 嫌いなんだね
Is your school super strict?
Too far for the sunshine
of summer to reach...
校則 厳しいとか？
No, I'd say it's on the liberal side.
いえ 比較的
自由な校風だと思いますけど
Trapped by the powerful gravity...
And the culture festivals are lots of fun!
文化祭とかも盛り上がりますし
Aw, lucky!
いいなあ～
Our school's pretty strict,
あたしらの学校
結構 厳しめだから
文化祭とかも お堅い感じなんだよ
and the culture festivals are super uptight.
It's mostly science project
posters and stuff.
An Observation on the
Lifecycle of the Honeybee
Phylum: Arthropoda  Class: Insecta
Order: Hymenoptera  Family: Apidae
Genus: Apis  Scientific Name: Apis
An Investigation into the Weight of
Ragworms Based on Environment
Phylum: Annelida  Class: Polychaeta
Order: Phyllodocida  Family: Nereididae
Genus: Hediste  Scientific Name: Hediste
ポスター 研究の展示とかばっかで
Really?
そっか
That's right. Shimo-Kitazawa High
is a prep school, isn't it?
下北沢高校って
進学校ですもんね
You two must be really smart!
じゃあ ２人とも頭いいんですね！
I'm pretty average, myself...
いや～ 別に あたしは普通だし
リョウは… ね？
And Ryo is... yeah.
Eh?
えっ？
You bombed your last round of tests, right?
この前のテスト
全部 赤点だったよね？
うん
えっ？
Yep.
Eh?
She picked the school for
the same reason I did:
あたしと同じ高校選んだ理由
because it was close to home!
家から近いからだもんね？
Yep.
そう
But then how did you pass the entrance exam?
でも それじゃあ
どうやって受験 合格したんです？
Ryo's a cram-the-night-before type.
リョウは完全に
一夜漬けタイプだから
She worked really hard right before the exam,
受験前は相当 頑張ってたけど
もう全部 忘れちゃったみたいでさ
but apparently forgot it all after.
When I study too hard,
I forget how to play bass.
勉強 頑張ると
ベースの弾き方 忘れる
Which means Ryo-senpai isn't
mysterious and thoughtful at all...
まさか リョウ先輩って
ミステリアスで
思慮深いわけではなく…
ふんふん…
No! Her brain is so small you can hear it
rattling around in her skull!
いやあ！　脳みそが小さくて
頭の中で転がる音がする～
Maybe we can use that sound in a new song!
この音 新曲で使えるかな？
Stop it! Stop destroying my fantasy!
やめて！
私のイメージを壊さないで！
Don't yell on the train.
電車の中では お静かに
I'm deleting this conversation
from my memory!
今の会話は記憶から消去します
Is this what overly strong love does to you?
人は愛が強すぎると
こうなっていくのか
じ… 時空が ゆがむ
あっ
C-Curvature of spacetime...
で ぼっちちゃんには
今 何が見えているの？
What are you seeing right now, Bocchi-chan?
I don't get why she's so isolated at school.
学校で ぼっちなの不思議
She's so fun.
こんなに面白いのに
ねっ！　ぼっちちゃんが
本当は すごい子って
Right?
I wish everyone at her school
could see how cool she is.
学校のみんなに
分かってもらえるといいね
I'll make sure to talk to her
when school starts again.
新学期からは
私も ちょくちょく
会いに行ってみます
You totally should!
そうしてあげて
Bocchi-chan's dream right now
is to drop out of school!
ぼっちちゃんの今の夢
高校中退だし
Does that even count as a dream?!
それ 夢って言っていいんですか？
Anyway, let's use today to make a fun
summer memory with Bocchi-chan!
とにかく
今日は ぼっちちゃんと
楽しい夏の思い出を作ろう！
うう…
Let's take a picture, Gotoh-san!
写真撮りましょ 後藤さん
ううう…
じゃ 塩ソフト
食べてくるので またね
I'm gonna get some sea salt
soft-serve. See you later.
Hey! No one said this was free time!
こら！　誰が自由行動って言った？
Gotoh-san. Please wake up already!
後藤さん いいかげん起きて
後藤さ～ん
うっ
Gotoh-san!
Look!
ほら見て！
ん？
The beach is so big!
海デカ～い！
ハッ！　あ… あれ？
いっ いつの間に…
H-Huh?
Wh-When did I...
You've really been out cold this whole time?
ホントに今まで意識なかったんだ
あ… ありがとう 喜多さん
Th-Thank you, Kita-san.
When was the last time I've been to the beach?
海なんて いつぶりだろう
いざ来てみると
やっぱり きれいで…
Now that I'm here,
I can see how beautiful it—
ねえ お姉ちゃんたち！
Hey, girls!
うわっ！
Come eat at our beach shack!
暇なら
うちの海の家で食べてきなよ～
We got a discount for cuties like you!
I-It's a party animal in the flesh!
じ… 実物のリアルパリピ！
We can get you a table for four right away!
あわわわ…
Are y'all in high school?
Where'd you come from?
お姉ちゃんたちＪＫ？
どっから来たの～？
あっ！
ひっ！
ぼっちちゃんが爆発四散した！
Bocchi-chan exploded!
Archetypal beach bros.
絵に描いたようなウェイ系だった
They're too powerful for us to handle!
あれを相手にするのは
分が悪すぎる！
Let's get away from the beach, ASAP!
急いで海から離れましょう！
Asahi Shop
まいどあり
Thanks for coming.
Here, for you, Gotoh-san.
はい これ 後藤さんの
Th-Thanks...
あ… どうも
Enoshima Fried
Tako Senbei
Asahi Shop
What is this?
これは？
Takosen!
たこせん
I hear they press the takoyaki
with a full ton of force!
たこを１トンの力で
プレスするんだって
A ton of force?
１トンの力…
おいしい
It's good!
私 おいしいものセンサーも抜群
My tastiness sensor never fails.
V-Very impressive!
さ… さすがです
Bocchi-chan, I'm just glad
to see you feeling better!
ぼっちちゃん
とにかく元気になってよかったよ
これ おっきくて かわいいし
映えますね！
It's so big and cute!
So photogenic!
Let's take a picture!
よし 写真撮ろ～！
Okay! Here comes the selfie!
は～い 撮りますよ！
Lemme see!
見せて 見せて
めっちゃいい感じです
It turned out super great!
I ate tako senbei with them.
みんなと食べた たこせんべい…
Summer memories...
夏の思い出
Th-Thank you...
あっ 今日は…
ん？
Thank you for today.
今日は ありがとうございました
お疲れさまでした
It's been wonderful.
なんで もうクライマックスに？
How are we at the climax already?!
And so, my summer came to an end.
こうして 私の夏は 終わった…
We're just getting started!
これからでしょ！
Enoshima Shrine
うわあ… ああ～
よ～し
ここから頂上まで登りますよ！
Okay! Let's climb all the way to the top!
えっ！　階段…
Enoshima Shrine
Stairs?
自力で上がって見る景色ほど
Is there anything more beautiful
than scenery you have to work to see?
すてきなものは
ないと思いませんか？
いや そんなのはいい
No. Screw that.
Let's do it!
頑張りましょう！
嫌だ！
No!
You too, Gotoh-san!
後藤さんも
あっ うっ…
伊地知先輩は行けますよね？
You'll come with me, right, Ijichi-senpai?
I'm not super into it either...
あたしも そんなに乗り気では…
ううっ！
Kita-chan! She's glowing more than ever!
喜多ちゃん いつになく まぶしい！
H-How?
な… なんで？
P-Perhaps her usually
understated extrovert aura
いっ いい… いつもは
抑え気味な陽のオーラが
ひ… 日の光を
浴びることによって…
h-has been amplified
by the light of the sun!
It's stripped off her limiter, you mean?!
リミッター解除されているのか！
Come on! Let's do it!
ほら 行きますよ
Kit-aura
あああ…
アハハハ
フッ フフフッ
Hurry up, everyone!
皆さ～ん 早く～！
もう無理　登れない
I'm done. No more climbing.
Kita-chan's getting further
and further ahead...
喜多ちゃんから
どんどん離されていく
うっ あああ…
うわああああ～
I'm out!
もう無理～
Who cares about the view?
景色とか知らん
どうでもいい
Not me.
ううっ うう…
Hang in there, you two.
２人とも しっかりしてください
まだ始まったばかりですよ
We've only just started!
Lemme take a break first.
ひとまず休憩させて～
What'll I do with you?
しかたないですね
You've got so much energy, Kita-chan...
喜多ちゃん 元気だね
うう…
あっ
E-Escar...
エ… エスカー
ん？
I th-think we can ride an escalator up!
エッ エス… エスカレーターで
行けるみたいですよ
おお～っ！
C'mon, let's climb the stairs!
階段で登りましょうよ！
Money Added:
Purchase Price:
Change:
C
Sea Candle Set
Adult
Trip down is
by stairs only
C  (Minor)
Sea Candle Set
Elementary Student
B
Escar Full Trip
Adult
B (Minor)
Escar Full Trip
Elementary Student
えっ お金かかるの？
It costs money?
江の島エスカーに乗るには
チケット買わないと
You need to buy tickets
to the Enoshima Escar.
ぐぬぬぬ…
だから 階段で登りましょ
See, we should climb the stairs instead!
Welcome!
いらっしゃいませ
I... I have no money, but...
い… 今 お金がなくて
I've got some pretty good bass guitars.
ベース！　私
いいやつ 結構持ってるんですけど
I'll give you one.
えっ？
１本 差し上げますから
Um, I don't think...
いや その…
２本ですか？
３本がお望みですか？
How about two?
You want three?!
いや まずはチケットを…
You need to buy a ticket...
What a breeze!
ハア～ 楽ち～ん
But climbing the stairs would have
made the view so much more impressive.
階段で登ったほうが
絶対 感動するのに
ら… 来月 お金返してくださいね
Y-You'll pay me back next month, right?
私は約束 破ったことない
I've never broken a promise in my life.
You didn't pay me back last time, though.
前の返してもらってないです
う…
Sorry, Bocchi-chan!
ごめんね ぼっちちゃん
バイト代の中から払わせるから
I'll take it out of her paycheck.
You're inhuman!
そんな殺生な！
We made it!
やっと着いた～
As long as we're here,
let's hit up the observation deck!
せっかくですし このまま
展望台まで上がりましょう
Even taking the Escar is kind of exhausting.
エスカー使ったとはいえ 疲れたね
It was... quite a long way.
結構 距離あった
Yeah...
ですね
But being up this high
feels quite liberating.
でも いざ上まで来ると
なんか開放的になる
P-Positivity wells up within me.
あっ なんかポジティブな気持ちに
なってきました
That's the fresh air and
magnificent view at work!
最高の眺めと空気だね！
Sh-Should we take a picture together?
み… みんなで写真撮ります？
ヘイ チーズ！
Yeah! Cheese!
Cheese!
チーズ！
They're finally getting into it.
急にハイテンションに
なり始めた…
見て見て～ きれい！
Look! Isn't it pretty?
ああ うん
Yeah, sure.
Hey. Aren't you listening?
Tropical Love
ちょっと 何ボーッとしてんの？
Oh, sorry.
あっ ごめん
You're just so pretty
I forgot everything else!
みーたん きれいだから
見とれちゃって
もう バカ
You silly!
Miitan!
みーたん
たっくん
Takkun!
Miitan!
みーたん…
The observation deck!
展望台！　展望台 行きましょ！
Takkun!
Let's go to the observation deck!
うわ～ 見てください！
Look at that!
The view from the observation deck
is even more fabulous!
展望台からの眺めは
更に絶景ですね！
目に焼き付けとかないと
We've really got to drink it all in!
ハア～ クーラー最高
I love air conditioning.
ん？
極楽
It's heaven.
S-Sure is.
で… ですね
Err, You guys?
あの 皆さん？
Long, long ago, humans attempted
to build a tower to heaven
昔々
人間は 神と対等になろうと
to prove themselves equal to God.
天まで届く高い塔を建てようとし
怒った神は
人間の言語をバラバラにし
God, enraged, scrambled
the languages of humans,
and cast their lands into chaos.
地上を混乱に陥れた
Talking about the Tower of Babel?
ああ“バベルの塔”ね
B-But humans failed to learn
and built another tall tower like this?
そ… それから学ばず
また人は こんな高い建物を
Guys! The scenery!
皆さ～ん あの 景色を…
Kita-chan got what she wanted,
so let's blow this joint.
喜多ちゃん満足したみたいだし
降りよっか
G-Good idea.
えっ？
で… ですね
My favorite part was the air conditioning.
涼しいのは最高だった
あっ…
ああ… インドア人たちめ！
You filthy indoor types!
Ryo. Weren't you eating sea salt
soft-serve earlier?
リョウ さっき
塩ソフト食べてなかった？
アイスは無限に食べれる
I've always got room for ice cream.
P-Please pay me back for the ice cream, too.
あっ あの
アイス代も返してくださいね
What should we do next?
あとは何します？
I think we've had plenty of fun, don't you?
もう 結構 遊んだけどね
そうですか？
You think?
I feel like we need one more
memorable event...
まだ もうひとイベントくらい
足りてない気が…
ん～
I wanna eat shirasu-don, then!
じゃあ シラス丼 食べたい！
They were sold out at the place
where we had lunch!
お昼の店 売り切れだったし
Nah. Too full.
無理　おなか いっぱい
Since when were you in charge?
ホントに自由だな おい
What's that sound?
この音 なんですか？
Oh, the kites?
ああ トンビじゃない？
They like to steal human food, so—
人の食べ物 狙ってくるので
気をつけ…
わっ！
Right as we were talking about it!
言ったそばから！
You okay, Bocchi-chan?
ぼっちちゃん 大丈夫？
あああ…
Gotoh-san, you want my ice cream?
後藤さん 私のアイス食べる？
うわああ～！
きゃあ～！
They're targeting Bocchi-chan!
ぼっちちゃんが獲物にされてる！
She looks weak!
It pisses me off.
Teach her a lesson!
ひい～っ！
鳥にまでナメられてる
Even birds look down on her.
Even birds?!
鳥にまでって…
Gotoh-san, you okay?
後藤さん 大丈夫？
It's over.
無理です
Get lost!
あっち行け～！
Memorable event achieved.
ひとイベントあった
That's not the kind of memorable I wanted!
私 こんなイベントは
望んでないです！
あんまり遅くなっても あれだし
そろそろ帰ろっか
But we can't stay out too late,
so we really should head out.
ぼっちちゃんも満身創痍だし
Bocchi's in bad shape, anyway.
Then how about a shrine visit
before we head home?
じゃあ 最後に
お参りだけして帰りませんか？
Enoshima Benzaiten
ここに祭られているのは
This shrine is dedicated to a goddess
called Myo-on Benzaiten.
妙音弁財天という女性の神様で
She's the goddess of music
and performing arts.
音楽 芸能の神様なんです
みんなで江の島 来れるなら
I've always thought we should come here
if we ever went to Enoshima together.
絶対 行きたいって 前から思ってて
じゃあ あたしたちのバンドの
今後の活躍を お願いしないと！
We'll have to wish for
our band's future success!
フフッ
Bocchi-chan.
ぼっちちゃん
さっき すごく真剣に
お願いしてたね
You looked like you were wishing
pretty hard back there.
え…
長かった
It took forever.
What were you wishing for?
何をお願いしたんですか？
I was wishing and thanking her
pretty hard too!
あたしは真面目に
お願いと お礼しちゃった
"Goddess, thanks for making
our concert a success.
“神様 ライブ 成功させてくれて
ありがとう”
Keep that good fortune coming!"
“これからも
よろしくお願いします”って
R-Really?
そ… そうですか
明日から練習 頑張るぞ！
Let's get back to practice tomorrow!
Even though we don't have
a next concert scheduled!
まだ次のライブ
決まってないけど～！
I can't tell them...
言えない
Please, Goddess!
神様 お願いします！
Turn back time to the first day of summer!
夏休み初日に
時間を戻してください
なんでもするから戻してください
I'll do anything, just turn back time!
それか 一生 食うに困らない
巨万の富と名声を！
Either that, or give me fame and fortune
so that I never go hungry!
...that I made a really vapid wish!
めっちゃ不毛なお願い
していただなんて！
ここから下北まで１時間くらい？
It's about an hour from here
to Shimo-Kita, right?
Yeah.
ですね
あっ 後藤さんだけ
藤沢で乗り換えね？
Gotoh-san, you'll change
trains at Fujisawa, right?
Y-Yes.
あっ はい
ん？
あっ…
Wake me up at Shimo-Kita.
下北 着いたら 起こして
Oh, they're hopeless!
しょうがないですねえ
あ～あ 本当は
鎌倉も観光したかったし
I really wish we'd gotten to do
some Kamakura sightseeing,
and I wish we'd had dinner together, too!
みんなで晩ご飯
したかったんだけどな～
Shirasu-don...
シラス丼…
あっ
She really wanted to eat that, huh?
よっぽど食べたかったみたい
My first long trip in a while...
久しぶりの遠出 楽しかったな
That was lots of fun.
I almost wish we could've
stayed out a little longer.
私も もう少しだけ
遊びたかったかも
Okay!
よ～し！
ん？
冬休みは全部 結束バンドの
みんなだけで遊びましょう！
Let's spend all of winter break
hanging out as Kessoku Band!
えっ…
後藤さん どこ行きたい？
Where do you want to go, Gotoh-san?
Let's make memories together
every single day!
毎日 思い出 作りましょうね！
そっ そんな毎日は
外出したくない！
I d-don't wanna go outside every day!
か… 考えておきます
I'll th-think about it...
Sure!
うん！
あっ 後藤さんも
眠かったら起こすけど
You can rest if you want, Gotoh-san.
I'll wake you up.
あ… いや 行きの電車で
ずっと意識なかったので
A-Actually, I spent the whole
train ride up here unconscious,
割と目は さえてて
so I'm pretty alert now.
Really?
そう？　じゃあ 藤沢まで
まだまだ楽しいが続くのね
Then the fun continues until Fujisawa!
エヘッ
H-Hey... Kita-san?
あっ あの 喜多さん
ん？
I e-enjoyed hanging out with you all today.
きょ… 今日は
みんなと遊べて楽しかったです
I th-think I can face school
starting tomorrow.
明日から頑張れそうです 多分…
Probably.
あ… 本当？　よかった！
Really? I'm glad to hear it!
Let's enjoy the new term together, too!
新学期も 一緒に楽しみましょうね
はい
Sure.
ウフフッ
This memory of summer will fuel me
through to winter break.
この夏の思い出を支えに
冬休みまで乗り切ろう！
Hitori-chan! It's morning!
ひとりちゃ～ん 朝よ～
I'm coming in!
入るよ～
You're still in bed?
まだ寝てるの？
新学期早々 遅刻するわよ
You'll be late to school your first day back!
Don't feel good. Wanna stay home.
具合悪いから 今日 休む…
Oh, Hitori-chan. Lying again
just to get out of school!
もう ひとりちゃん
学校行きたくないからって
またウソついて
N-No...
ちっ ちが…
Help me out, Futari!
M-My muscles are so sore,
I can't even move!
ぜ… 全身 筋肉痛で動けない！
Okay!
ワン ワン
あっ…
Wake up, Sis!
ほ～ら お姉ちゃん　起きて
No, no, no, no!
ダメ ダメ ダメ…
あああ～っ！
Morning!
おはよ～！
おは～
Morning!
Hey, Kita-chan, I saw your
Issta photos of Enoshima!
ねえねえ 喜多ちゃん
イソスタに上げた
江の島の写真 見たよ
31st Annual
Shuka Festival
Stage performers wanted!
October 1st & 2nd
Location: Shuka High School Gym
Please place requests for stage time
in the box in front of the student council room
prior to the deadline.
A participant interview will take place after applications are received.
Participant groups will also need to explain stage crew requirements.
Feel free to ask questions!
Application deadline: September 16th
Planning/Organization: Shuka High School
Culture Festival Executive Committee
え～ ありがとう！
Really? Thanks!
What's wrong with not
letting my sound die down?
What's wrong with being young?
Hey, why doesn't it stop?
The rhythm that I can't stop
keeps reverberating through my body
The melody playing in my earphones
is the only thing that lets me be who I am
The sky is tinged in red
But what color is my soul?
Tell me
where should I go?
I've always been searching
for something precious (hey!)
If everything's going to be lost some day
let's engrave it as deep as we can (now!)
My most pathetic nights
and cackling laughter
And days when I couldn't say
more than "You know..."
(I'm alive now, yeah Springtime of life)
What's wrong with not
letting my sound die down?
What's wrong with being young?
#10 After Dark
Watch it!
見てください！